To go from the periphery to the depth, I already place
为了从外周到深层，我将
my thumbs
我的拇指已经
in a certain way in the orientation of my ventricles.
以某种方式沿着我的脑室方向。
I make contact first with the texture of the hair.
我首先接触头发的质地。
And then without really moving, I wait a little bit
然后，我几乎不动，稍等片刻
until I feel the
直到我感觉到
and I feel my hands, you see, warming up a bit, getting...
并且感觉到我的手，你看，有点发热，它们开始...
getting...
...
There, it's starting to change.
好了，它开始变化了。
I feel, I feel a difference.
我感觉到，我感觉到一种不同。
Did you feel the moment it appeared?
你感觉到它出现的那一刻了吗？
And suddenly, there, it's the bone.
砰，突然间，那里是骨头。
Here, I have a lot of receptors in my hands.
在这里，我的手中有许多感受器。
Hello friends, there you go.
大家好，就是这样。
We're going to use them and at the same time, the hand emits heat.
我们将利用它们，同时，手会散发热量。
Now, I'm going to go in very gently.
现在，我将非常缓慢地进入。
I'm going to go from the hair, to the skin, to the fascia, to the bone.
我将从头发，到皮肤，到筋膜，再到骨骼。
I'm still on the bone.
我仍然在骨骼上。
And now, there, it's starting to pass to the left.
而现在，好了，它开始向左侧移动了。
I'm gently entering to pass.
我非常缓慢地渗透进去。
I enter, I go into a sensation, a perception, it's
我进入，我进入一种感觉，一种感知，这是一种频率。
a frequency.
好了，骨骼变得如此流畅，我从后面进入。
There, the bone becomes fluid like that, I
不要忘记骨骼是中胚层，所以它是一种中胚层组织，它是一个层
go behind.
直达大脑。
Don't forget that bone is mesoderm, so it's a mesodermal tissue, it's a layer
好了，我到达一个液体腔室，我开始感觉到。
that goes all the way to the brain.
我将稍微退后，我真的将稍微退后。
There, I'm reaching a liquid compartment, I'm starting to feel it.
退后是为了更好地跳跃。
I'm going to take a step back, I'm really going to take a step back.
这确实是这里的浅表层，漩涡。
Take a step back to jump better.
Prendre du recul pour mieux sauter.
It's really the superficial layer here, the vortex.
C'est vraiment la couche superficielle ici, le vortex.
Here we see the arachnoid, with the
这里我们看到蛛网膜，以及蛛网膜柱。
arachnoid pillars.
蛛网膜柱。
Here I started to have a sensation of the hemispheres.
在这里，我开始感受到大脑半球。
Now we're going to go a little further.
现在我们要再深入一点。
And we're going to play with the ventricles.
我们将感受脑室。
We're going to feel her brain.
我们将感受她的大脑。
She just had another sensation, did you feel that?
她刚刚有了另一种感觉，你感受到了吗？
Yes, it's like a closing.
是的，这就像一种闭合感。
To show you, I'm going to kind of induce.
为了向你们展示，我将稍微引导一下。
Like a little dolphin, you see on the right, breathing a little less well.
就像一只小海豚，你看到右侧呼吸不太顺畅。
You just have to give it space.
只需要给予它空间。
which will allow it to breathe better.
这将使它能够更好地呼吸。
I'm coming back out layer by layer.
我将逐层退出。
That way, it's not straight.
这样，它就不正了。
There, Miss, please describe your perception a little.
好的，女士，请您描述一下您的感知。
At the level, when I really got to the bone,
在骨骼层面，当我真正到达骨骼层面时，
I really had this sensation of being impacted.
我真的有一种受到冲击的感觉。
And after, it became...
然后，它就...
it became much lighter, after when
变得更轻盈了，之后当
you went underneath, and the movement
你深入下方时，以及
of the hemispheres is very, very, very pleasant, and we could clearly feel the difference between left
大脑半球的运动非常非常舒适，我们清楚地感受到了左右之间的差异，
and right, at the level of the ventricles, and then finally, the frequency
在脑室层面，最后，频率
which was
它曾是
more electric, it resembled a very fast vibration, but
像电流般的，它就像一种非常快速的振动，但是
not sharp. There, are you guiding yourself on that?
不刺痛。好的，您能对此进行引导吗？